alltimetv.com 2015-06-09

# Site5 - Privacy Policy

Site5.com ("Site5") has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy to our customers and users of our consulting services, online services, websites, and web services ("Services").

This privacy policy governs the manner in which Site5 uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its customers and users of our Services.

### 1\. Privacy

Site5 is committed to developing long lasting relationships based on trust. As such, Site5 will do everything in its power to ensure that your right to privacy is maintained and protected. Our Services are not directed at children under 13 years of age.

### 2\. Information We Collect

Site5 may request or collect personal information from online users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where users are invited to volunteer such information.

The information we collect is personal information that identifies you personally, such as:

  * First & last name
  * Postal address
  * Telephone and fax numbers
  * URL
  * E-mail address
  * Credit card information
  * Other billing information

Site5 may also collect information about how users access our Services using a tracking ID unique to each user through the use of cookies or other similar means.

### 3\. What are Cookies?

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer’s hard drive for an extended period of time.

Your browser’s help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by Site5 to track user preferences while the user is using our Services. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. Persistent cookies may be used by Site5 to store whether, for example, you want your password remembered or not, and other information. Cookies used on Site5 websites do not contain personally identifiable information.

### 4\. Log Files

Like most standard websites, we use log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in our log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information.

### 5\. How we use this Information

Site5 may use the personally identifiable information collected by Site5 to contact customers regarding products and services offered by Site5 and, to the extent the User has agreed to it, by its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners.

We may also use this information for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our Services and marketing and sales efforts. Site5 will not in any way share this information with a third party either for free or by selling it, unless you specifically authorize such disclosures.

### 6\. Disclosure of Information

Site5 may also disclose aggregate, anonymous, data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. In such cases, statistical information only will be disclosed and personally identifiable data will be kept strictly confidential. In case Site5 is sold, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners.

Site5 may from time to time engage third parties, including its own subsidiaries and affiliated companies, to preserve, analyze or otherwise store or manipulate data received by Site5 from its customers. In all such cases, such third party service providers will be required to treat all such data with the same degree of care as Site5 and they will be prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy.

### 7\. Special Offers and Updates

Our customers and users will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and possibly a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

### 8\. Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement, if, for instance, our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

### 9\. Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary and required to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on Site5.

Site5 websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Site5 is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. The Site5 Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by Site5.

### 10\. Maintenance of Information

The information provided to Site5 is saved indefinitely and may be stored on one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by Site5. Site5 employs industry standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information.

While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur; we make every effort to prevent such occurrences. Any other particularly sensitive information, such as credit card numbers collected for commercial transactions, is encrypted prior to transmission by you to Site5.

### 11\. Safe Harbor

Site5 has certified its participation and compliance with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the transfer of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland to the United States. The principles of Safe Harbor compliance are notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. Additional information about the Safe Harbor principles and certification process can be found at the US Department of Commerce's [Safe Harbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/) website.

Site5 has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Safe Harbor, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Site5, please visit the BBB EU Safe Harbor [web site](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint.

### 12\. Your Responsibility

You are responsible for the security of the login information, such as usernames and passwords, which give you access to your private information maintained by Site5. Make sure you keep login information in a safe place and do not share it with others.

Note that key-loggers, viruses, or other surveillance devices can intercept login information on the computers from which you access our Services, so you should take precautions regarding such devices, especially from public computers. In addition, you should always log out from any relevant Services when you are not actively using them.

### 13\. Questions

Any questions concerning this Privacy Policy may be directed to .
